Võ Thành Nhơn (1994), Software Engineer

mail@tedvo.dev | (+84) 793 090994 | Ho Chi Minh, Ho CHi Minh, VN

linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ted-vo | github: https://github.com/ted-vo | Telegram:

https://telegram.me/ted_vo

SUMMARY

I graduated with software engineer. Begin at Android Developer. And then, I work with NodeJS as Backend Developer. As an Android Developer with 4 years of experience and 2 years of experience as an Backend Developer. For now and future, I am focusing on SRE (Site Reliability Engineer). I have 2 years experience with SRE.

EDUCATION

Posts and Telecommunication Institute of Technology, Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

The Degree of Engineer - Software Development

2012-09-05 — 2018-04-01

SKILLS

SRE (*Senior*): GCP, Helm, Cloudflare, Linux, Kubernetes, Shell, Terraform, Docker, Golang, Istio, Envoy, Linkerd, DataDog, Grafana, Clickhouse, Elasticsearch, MySQL, Redis, Gitlab CI/CD

Backend Developer (Senior): Java, Nodejs, Golang, Mongodb, SQL, Cryptocurrency, Microservices

Android Developer (*Senior*): Java, Kotlin, Cryptocurrency

.....

EXPERIENCE

Inspirelab (closed) | Site Reliability Engineer

2022-04-02 — 2024-11-30

Closed

Setup and manage infrastructure

- Manage GCP (Google Cloud Platform) infras.
- Using terraform manage infras as code: Network, IAM, GKE, GCE, Storage, Secret Manager, KMS, CloudRun, CloudSQL, CloudFunction.
- Setup Gitlab self host runner for CI/CD.
- Setup git workflows and centralize CI/CD workflows for apps.
- Using helm-chart manage configure and deloyment Golang app built-in config with infras. Optional built-in with sidecar: sevicemesh (istio, linkerd), redis, DataDog.
- Using shellscript devlop internal tool for backend developer setup local environment. Limit and grant permission to access dev environment and internal apps.
- Monitoring GCP Resources to balance workload with cost.
- Research OpenOberve to planning replace DataDog for optimize cost.
- Contribute to build architecture backend systems.

Inspirelab (closed) | Back End Developer

2021-06-02 - 2022-04-01

Closed

Develop new features

- Language using is Java 17
- Maintenance and develop new feature of ICO (Initial coin offering) system
- Fixed critical bug of forgot password feature.
- Develop user referral feature
- Develop reward cryptocurrency pool prize for game portal.

Inspirelab (closed) | Android Leader

2021-04-19 — 2021-06-01

Form new Android team with 2 members to build super application for gaming platform.

- Structure architecture of the super application like Grab but for gaming.
- Manage and assign tasks for team member.
- Develop SDK for app in app

Vitalify Asia | Android Developer

2019-10-10 — 2021-04-15

https://vitalify.asia

Closed

Maintenance and develop outsoure projects

- Maintenance Golf Club application.
- Develop new healthcare application. The application sync data from healthcare device via BLE.
- Maintenance SDK of the ads ecosystem. The SDKs contact with the device via BLE. Restruct the new version of SDK with simple integration and high-performance.
- Develop the new plugin SDK for application build with Cordova.

 $\textbf{Finance Technology Solutions (closed)} \mid \text{Android Developer}$

2019-03-01 — 2019-09-01

Closed

Develop new features

• Develop tradingviews and charts for cryptocurrency application. Stockchart (time-line, k-line, macd, kdj, rsi...)

Horical (closed) | Fullstack Developer

2017-09-01 - 2019-02-28

Closed

Maintenance a outsoure project and develop 2 product projects

- Maintenance car fixing service application.
- Develop Coffee-shop management system.
- Develop ERP client android application.

LANGUAGES

Vietnamese (*Native*), English (*Limited working proficiency*), Chinese (*No proficiency*)

.....

INTERESTS

Computer [Computer Science , Open Source] , Fitness [Hiking/Camping] , Music [Drums , Guitar]